这玩意儿显然没用了
Well, that thing's clearly in the way.
好吧  嗯哼
All right. A-ha. Heh.
死冰箱
Damn fridge!
嗨  乔伊  你好吗  很好啊
Hi, Joey. How you doing? Great...
室友
...roomie. Ah!
我们现在的确是室友  没错  你这么一提醒
Yeah, I guess we are roommates now. Yeah! Well, now that you brought it up...
那个  我们的冰箱坏了  得买台新的
...uh, our fridge is broken. We have to get a new one.
我打听过  你付一半400元   感激不尽
Now, I checked around and your half is $400. Thanks a lot.
我才不付呢
I'm not paying for half of that.
等我公寓修好了  我就搬回去了
I'm only staying here until my apartment gets fixed.
瑞秋  这台冰箱是我出生之后  父母给买的
Look, Rach, my parents bought this fridge just after I was born. Okay?
我用一直都没问题   你一来它就坏了
Now, I have never had a problem with it. Then you show up and it breaks!
这说明什么
What does that tell you?
说明冰箱不能和人一样长寿
That refrigerators don't live as long as people?
好了  你也知道自动提款机一次只能提300元
All right, now you know that the ATM only lets you take out 300 at a time...
剩下的100   我就收支票了
...so I'll take a check for the other 100.
你在开玩笑   对吧
Heh. You're joking, right?
那当然  我不收支票
Of course I'm joking. I don't take checks.
幸好你还长的帅
Thank God you're pretty.
老友记  第六季  第19集  乔伊的冰箱
Friends  S06E19  The One With Joey's Fridge
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
（中央咖啡厅）
嘿  嘿
Hey! Hey.
你们有认识的帅哥吗
Hey, do You guys know any cute guys?
当然有  就是我的好朋友乔伊
Well, of course, I do. My good friend, Joey, over here.
我忘了  谢谢你  钱德
Oh, I'm sorry. Thank you, Chandler.
周末有大型慈善晚会   罗夫罗兰买了一桌
Anyway, there's this big charity ball this weekend and Ralph Lauren bought a table...
我也得去
...so I kind of have to go.
为什么募捐啊   不知道
What's the charity? I don't know.
不是某种树   就是某种病
Something, either trees or disease,
罗夫很会碎碎念
Ralph mumbles a lot.
罗夫都趁你不专心时碎碎念吗   对呀   好奇怪
Does Ralph mumble when you're not paying attention? Yeah. It's weird.
总之  我得找个男伴
But the thing is, I need to find a date.
你想找什么样的人
Well, What kind of guy are you looking for?
自己有晚礼服或租得起晚礼服
Well, Someone that has his own tux or has the ability to rent a tux.
必须是男人  身家起码要有50元
So he has to be a male who has at least $50.
噢  只差一点点
Ooh, so close.
大家好   嗨
Hey, everybody. Hey.
这是伊丽莎白  嗨
Uh, this is Elizabeth. Hi, Elizabeth.
我就是那个学生
I'm the student. Ha-ha-ha.
真可爱啊  才怪
Isn't she cute?  No.
也许我不该多嘴   但你们不是不想在公共场所
Y'know, this is probably none of my business, but weren't you guys supposed...
被别人看到在一起吗   我们没有在一起
...to not be seen in public together? Oh, we're not together.
没有  我们只是  在咖啡馆
No. We're just two people who happen to have run into each other...
巧遇的两个人而已
...here at the coffee house. Heh, this is--
噢  真狡猾
Oh, sly.
我真想好好认识你们   不过我该走了
Well, I really wanted to meet you guys, but I have to run.
改天见  好
I'll see you later? Okay.
罗斯  再见  再见
Bye, Ross. Bye. See you.
我不是故意撞到你的  先生  没关系  女士
Oops! I did not mean to run into you like that, sir. That is quite all right, ma'am.
拜
Bye.
她干吗走了   要上晚自习还要去赶作业
So why's she leaving? Is it a school night and she has a lot of homework to do?
对  她明天要交分子流行病学报告
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.
帮我祝她好运
Well, tell her "good luck" with that.
还有吗   别客气
Anyone else, huh? Bring them on.
她什么时候生日   我不知道   瑞秋  干吗问呢
Oh! When's her birthday? I don't know, Rachel. Why?
我好久没吃儿童生日餐了
Well, you know it's just been so long since I've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
我喜欢伊丽莎白  谢谢
I like Elizabeth. Well, thanks.
我真的很喜欢她   叫她今年早点送曲奇饼干来
In fact, I like her so much that you tell her I want my cookies early this year.
要薄荷巧克力饼和巧克力派
Y'know, A box of Thin Mints and some Tag-a-longs.
你们别整他了  说真的  你们交往得怎样
Hey-hey come on you guys, give him a break. Ross, seriously, how's it going with her?
非常好啊
Well, actually it's been great.
她才20岁   还不想太认真
She's 20, so she's not looking for anything too serious...
最适合现在的我
...which is perfect for me right now.
太好了  她真的好像很不错
Well, that is great. And seriously, she seems very nice.
谢谢   我知道你们喜欢涮我
Thanks. I know you guys like to give me a hard time and all,
但我真的希望你们能喜欢她
...but it really means a lot to me that you like her.
只要知道你们  我想到一个很棒的
Just knowing that you guys are, like. Okay, I got a good one.
好
Okay, um-Heh.
她是才12岁吗
What is she, like, 12?
钱德   你觉得我们的沟通够吗
Chandler, do you think we talk about our relationship enough?
够了  有水果卷吗
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll Ups?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
好  我刚想到一个人  很适合当瑞秋的男伴
Okay, I just thought of the perfect guy for Rachel to take to her thing.
有意思  我们也找到人了
Oh that's so funny, we found someone too.
那好  她可以在我的人和你们的怪胎之中选一个
Oh that's good. I guess she'll have a choice between my guy and your weirdo.
为什么我们的人是怪胎   因为你们的品味
Why would our guy be a weirdo? Because that's just your taste.
瑞秋才不会选你的蠢人
See, Rachel's not gonna pick your stupid guy.
是吗  没错
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
我这个是一个做义工的律师
My guy is a lawyer who does volunteer work.
而且他有这个东西
And he has one of these.
脸屁股
A face ass?
下巴窝啦   我们的这个是钱德的同事
A chin dimple. Well, uh, our guy works with Chandler.
他人好  聪明  又会打扮
And he's really nice and smart and he's a great dresser.
你们看过他的身体吗  没有  他是一颗飘来飘去的头
Have you seen your guy's body? No. Our guy's just a floating head.
我这个身材很赞   他是我的按摩客人
Well, my guy is spectacular, okay? He's a massage client.
有一次他在按摩台上  就被我看个精光光的
And one time, um, when he was on the table, I looked at it. And I mean, all of it.
你不是不能偷看吗   报警啊   来抓我啊
You're not supposed to look. Yeah, like there are police for that.
等等  你也给我按摩过  你会偷看  没错
Wait! you look? You massaged me. I know.
好  你那个或许有好身材  但我们这个
All right, your guy may have a great body, but our guy...
相当幽默   钱德式的幽默
is really funny. Chandler funny?
我们这个舞功高强   我这个饱读诗书
Our guy's a great dancer. My guy's well-read.
我们这个一头靓发   我这个两排洁牙
Our guy has great hair. My guy has great teeth.
我们这个香的不得了
Our guys smells incredible.
我们说的是一个人吗
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
你的脸色不太好   乔伊
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
冰箱坏了  我得把里面的东西都吃掉
Well, the fridge broke, so I had to eat everything.
冷盘  冰淇淋  橙汁
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
嘿   咖啡色罐子里装的是什么
Hey, what was in that brown jar?
那个还在  已经不在了
That's still in there? Not anymore.
那么  你准备付我多少钱
Ahem, so, anyway, how do you want to pay me?
你要提供某种服务吗
Is this a service you're providing me?
不是  是我要买新冰箱   我们的新冰箱
No, for my new fridge. For our new fridge.
我们的新冰箱
Our new fridge?
我都不在这里住了   那又怎样
I don't live here anymore. So what?
假设我们是离婚的夫妻
Look, okay, suppose we were a, uh, divorced couple.
我取得了孩子的监护权
Uh-huh. And I got custody of the kid. Right?
结果孩子死了  我总得买个新孩子
Now, suppose the kid dies and I gotta buy a new kid.
好
0Kay.
给我400元
Give me $400!
盖勒教授
Professor Geller? Hmm?
喔   一名我不认识的学生
Oh, a student I don't know.
我想问下   能不能跟您谈一会儿
I was wondering if I could talk to you for a moment?
当然可以  是哪方面的事
Yes, of course. What would this be regarding?
在你的研究室亲热一下  好
Making out in your office. Wh-Shh!
当然  我们进去谈如何
Uh, of course. Why don't we go inside.
噢  哦
Mm-Oh, oh.
怎么了  门把手   门把手
What? Doorknob. Doorknob.
抱歉
Sorry. Ha-ha-ha.
我真的有事要讲   好  什么事
Um, I actually do need to talk to you. Oh. Okay, what about?
春游   春游
Spring vacation. Spring vacation?
对   学校没课  很多人要出去旅行
Yeah, we have time off, and a lot of people are going on trips--
盖勒教授  是  菲森死盯个乐教授
Professor Geller. Yes, Professor Fiesenstinlender?
等我一分钟  我马上就好
I'll be with you in one moment.
那我就买一盒薄荷巧克力饼
So I will take one box of the Thin Mints.
你们不懂   伊丽莎白想找我跟她去旅行
You don't understand. Elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
你这样叫慢慢来吗   我还没准备好
Is that taking it slow? I'm not ready for this, okay?
我该怎么说   实话实说  说你还没准备好
What do I tell her? Tell her the truth. You're not ready.
我可以试试
I could do that.
要是她不高兴呢   你就拿芭比娃娃逗她
Well, what if she gets upset? Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
或者
Or...
你也可以  你知道的
...you could just, you know, you...
你这是在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
什么
What?
我干什么  你刚弄坏了我的冰箱
What the hell am I doing? You just broke my fridge!
什么  你怎么知道它坏了
What? How do you know if-How do you know it's even broken?
它怎么坏的我会不知道吗
Oh, you think I don't know what breaks my fridge?
等一下
Excuse me.
看嘛   坏了
Well, what do you know? Broken!
要赔400元
That'll be $400.
乔伊  我看见你推他了
Joey, I saw you push him.
是你推的
You pushed him.
乔伊  我没把它弄坏  它早就坏了
Joey, I did not break this. Okay? That has been broken for a while.
钱德   记不记得我提过这是我们的冰箱
All right. Chandler, do you remember how I told you about our fridge? Uh-huh.
我到现在还没收到你那一半钱
I still haven't gotten the check for your half yet.
不要给他钱
Do not give him any money.
你少插嘴   弄坏冰箱的家伙
I'm not talking to you! You broke my fridge!
盖勒教授   你找我  是的  请进
You wanted to see me, Professor Geller? Yes. Yes. Please come in.
噢  哦
Mm, ooh, ooh.
门把手  对  有点玩上瘾了
Doorknob? Yeah. It kind of grows on you.
事实上  我想和你谈谈春游的事
Actually, I wanted to finish talking to you about spring vacation.
喔   好
Oh, good.
听着  我
Look, L...
我跟你在一起很开心
Look, I've been having a great time with you.
我不想进展得太快   那样会给大家压力
And I just don't want us to move too fast or put too much pressure on us.
所以很抱歉   我们还不能一起出去旅行
So I'm sorry, I just don't think we should go away together yet.
那样太快了
It's too soon.
罗斯  你误会我的意思了
Uh, Ross, I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
我只是想告诉你   我要去佛罗里达州两星期
I just wanted to tell you that I'm going to Florida for a couple weeks.
不
No.
是你误会我的意思了
I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
我的意思是  你真的好可爱
What I meant was... You are so adorable.
这个  我们来谈谈可爱吧
That. Let's talk about that.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
和伊丽莎白谈得怎么样了  喔
How did it go with Elizabeth? Huh? Oh, oh.
没事  只是一场误会  她不是要我一起去
it was fine. It was just a misunderstanding. She didn't want me to go with her.
她只是要告诉我   她准备去佛州春游
She just wanted to let me know that she's going to Florida for spring vacation.
等等   她是去春游  还是去度春假
Wait, is she going for spring vacation or going for spring break.
有什么差别吗
What's the difference?
春游就是跟爷爷奶奶一起共享天伦
A spring vacation, you're doing nice things with your grandparents.
春假嘛   就是跟兄弟会的人上床
Spring break, you're doing frat guys.
不是每个人的春假都那样
Hey, you know what? Not all spring breaks are like that.
那你是怎么过的   我跟我爸去了埃及
What did you do on yours? I went to Egypt with my dad.
我能想像   "看  爸爸  狮身人面像"
I can see it now. "Look, Dad, it's the Sphinx."
我想伊丽莎白那么正经   不会去"春假"
I think Elizabeth is a little more serious than, "Spring break!"
好吗   她修了我的课
All right? Come on, she's taking my class.
还跟教授上床   我给她打电话
And slept with the professor. I'm gonna call her.
各位  这是塞巴斯蒂
Hey, you guys, I want you to meet Sebastian.
我们刚刚
Hi. We just, uh--
在报摊认识   我们同时抓起了一本《原野与河流》
We just met at the newsstand. We both grabbed for the last Field and Stream. Ha!
呃   我读过
What, I read that.
我去给你拿杯咖啡   好啊   谢谢
Can I get you a cup of coffee? Oh, yes. Thank you.
瑞秋  你这是什么意思  什么
Rachel, what the hell is this? What?
你叫我们帮你找男伴   却自己带了个人来
You ask us to find you a guy, and then you come in here with a guy of your own.
你们帮我找到人了  对
You found me a guy? Yes.
在钱德的公司  看中了一个可爱风趣的人
We found you a really cute, funny guy from Chandler's work.
我也找了一个   至少不是怪人
Yeah, and I found you one, too, who is not a weirdo.
我真的很感激你们
You know what though, guys, I really appreciate that...
不过我还是带塞巴斯蒂一起去舞会好了
...but I'm just gonna take Sebastian to the charity.
你确定   我们的这个浑身异香
Are you sure? Because our guy smells incredible.
别再提那个了好吗
Would you stop it with that already?
你的咖啡   谢谢
Here you go. Sure. Oh, thank you.
塞巴斯蒂   你是义工吗
So, Sebastian, do you do any volunteer work?
不是  怎么了  没事
Uh, no, not really. Why? No reason.
只是我认识一个   关心别人的单身好男人
It's just I know a single guy who does care about other people.
你风趣吗
Are you funny?
什么  你们这是在干吗
Excuse me? What are you guys doing?
你风趣吗   讲个笑话来听听
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
我只是想和瑞秋喝杯咖啡
Look, I just wanted to have coffee with Rachel.
是啊   很多人都想
Well, so do a lot of people.
说实话   我想我该走了
Actually, uh, I gotta get going. Oh, but you--
有空打电话   不过你没给我电话号码
Give me a call sometime. But you didn't give me your number.
那好  改天见
Okay, see you later.
原来他蛮风趣的
Turns out he is kind of funny.
我简直不能相信
I cannot believe you guys!
他这么好   就这样被你们赶走了
He was really nice and he just left because of you!
"塞巴斯蒂"   听起来像猫的名字
Yeah, but, "Sebastian"? What is that, a cat's name?
你知道我发现了什么   瑞秋  他很胆小
You know what I noticed, Rachel, he scares easy.
你难道带这样的人去舞会
Now, is that the kind of guy you want to take to a ball?
"塞巴斯蒂   要不要跳舞"
"Sebastian, would you like to dance?"
"好  我得走了"
"Uh, okay. I gotta go. Aah!"
够了  别说了   瑞秋  对不起
All right, guys stop it. Rachel, we're very sorry.
我们太过分了
That is a very insensitive thing for us to do.
这样吧  让我们补偿你   我们有两个好男人让你挑
You know what? Let us make it up to you. We've two really great guys for you.
对啊   你有什么损失
Yeah, what have you got to lose?
如果你选我这边的人   搞不好会认识让你心动的人
Y'know you might even end up with someone really special. If you pick my guy.
好吧  好   你愿意见我们找的人
All right. Okay. So you will meet our guys?
是啊   我愿意
Yes, I'll meet them.
你选谁都行   你自己决定
It doesn't matter which one you choose. y'know? It's completely up to you.
我们这个才叫完美
Our guy is perfect.
或者你也可以选
Or you could go out with the guy Phoebe deemed...
菲比看不上眼的人
...not good enough to go outwith herself. Ugh!
菲比  你在这儿   你弄坏我的冰箱
Phoebe, there you are! Okay, you broke my fridge.
欠我400元
You owe me 400 bucks.
好吧  真的
Okay, sure. Really?
技术上来说   你欠我600元   你最近十次的试镜
Ooh, technically, you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts...
我都有给你祝福
...on your last 10 auditions.
那就算扯平了
Call it even?
好吧
0Kay.
回来了  伊丽莎白怎么说
There you are. So, what did Elizabeth say?
她真的是要去德通纳  渡"春假  呼呼"
Well, turns out she is going to Daytona for "spring break, woo-hoo."
那就有湿衫美女大赛   男生会向女生身上射水
That means wet T-shirt contests, guys doing shots off of girls' bodies...
第二天醒来甚至不知道一起睡的是谁
...waking up next to people you don't even know.
看来  她会玩得很爽了
Man, she is gonna have a great time!
她要住可乐娜酒店吗
Is she staying at the Hotel Corona?
你熟悉那酒店  当然  我参加过81年春假  呼呼
You know the hotels? Sure! I was there, Spring Break '81! Woo-hoo!
81年  你才13岁
In 1981, you were 13.
那又怎样  我开车过去  卖了T恤  玩得好开心
So what? I drove down, sold T-shirts. I had a blast.
你们知道谁最会疯   醉酒的女大学生
And y'know who knows how to party? Drunk college chicks.
知道了  她不能去
Okay, she can't go.
罗斯  你不能阻止她去  你们这才交往多久啊
Ross, You can't tell her not to go. You just started dating.
那我该怎么办  不怎么办   你只能冷处理哦
Then what am I supposed to do? Nothing. Just be cool with it.
要是她跑去跟一堆人上床呢
What if she goes down there and sleeps with a bunch of guys?
那这次   你就别娶她了
Well, maybe you don't marry this one.
我真为你能去旅行而高兴
I'm so glad you're going on this trip.
就是啊   我这学期这么用功
Yeah, I've been working so hard this semester.
真的需要疯狂一下   好好缓解下压力
I really need to go crazy, you know? Blow off some steam.
当然   当然需要了
Sure. Sure.
我不知道你的计划到底定了没有
Look, I don't know if your plans are finalized yet...
但我知道  还有一个办法可以缓解压力
...but I know another great way to blow off steam.
什么办法  你喜欢做手工艺吗
What? Are you into crafts at all?
罗斯  你还好吗  我当然很好
Ross, are you okay? Uh, yeah. Of course I'm okay.
我只是在表示  支持
Heh, I'm just being, uh, supportive.
支持你和你的旅行
Supportive of you and this whole trip...
还有   这是这是什么
...and what-What is, uh--? What's this?
是泳衣啊   你要穿着它去见人
It's a bathing suit? To wear in front of people?
你这样算支持吗   这样是吗
Is that supportive? Is this?
嘿  太好了
Hey. Good, good, good.
嘿  嗨
Hey. Hi.
很高兴你答应见我们找的人   哦
We're glad you decided to meet our guy. Oh.
你一定会很喜欢他的
You're gonna like him so much.
你准备什么时候见他   不知道啊
So umm, when do you want to meet him? I don't know.
我明晚不加班   明晚不错
I don't work late tomorrow night. Tomorrow night is good.
不过  现在能做的事  为什么要拖到明天
but uh, y'know what? why put off something till tomorrow that you can do right now. Ha-ha-ha.
艾达   过来  什么
Eldad, come here! What?
艾达  这位是瑞秋  你好吗
Eldad, this is Rachel. How are you?
有点措手不及   不过我很好
A little blind-sided, but, you know, good.
艾达  来坐  你坐过去  坐过去
Eldad, sit down. Move over. Move over now.
行了   就坐这儿吧
There you go. There you are.
好了  好了  我们知道了
Okay! Okay! we can take a hint! Ha-ha-ha.
等等  你来干什么  这位是派屈克
Wait. What are you doing here? This is Patrick.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
你来晚了  她跟我们那个在一起了
Okay, you're too late okay? because she's already with our guy.
天哪  对啊  我是来晚了  他们正坐在沙发上聊天呢
Oh, my God, you're right, I am too late. They're sitting on the couch and talking.
拜托
Come on.
瑞秋  怎样   这是派屈克
Rachel?  Yeah?  This is Patrick. Yeah?
喔  嗨   嗨
Oh. Hi. Hi.
他就是我说的那个人
This is the guy I was telling you about.
相信我  这套西装  太委屈里面的一流身材了
Believe me, this suit does not do justice to what's underneath it.
懂了
0Kay.
但是菲比  什么  你们这样让我好为难
But Pheebs, Yeah? I'm just sort of in the middle of something.
没事的   没关系   你坐过来
Oh, okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
你不能这样   也许我得走了
You can't do that! Maybe I should go.
你坐下   我们赢定了
Just sit down, we're winning.
好吧  也许我该走了
Okay, you know what? Maybe I should go.
不  不要  你也给我坐下  坐下
No, no! Have a Seat! Have a seat!
瑞秋  你还没摸过艾达的头发
Rachel, Rachel, you haven't touched Eldad's hair.
超柔顺的  你摸摸看  不必了
It is the softest hair. Touch it. Yeah, I'm good.
瑞秋  派屈克很有钱   拿钱砸她
Rachel, Patrick is really rich. Give her some money.
菲比   这个免费按摩的代价太高了
Y'know what Phoebe? this isn't really worth the free massage.
没错   派屈克   再见
That's right, Patrick. Bye-bye.
艾达绝对是个好舞伴
Eldad is much more cooperative and he can dance.
跳个舞给瑞秋看看
You dance for Rachel.
不   拜托   别跳了
No-no! don't dance for me, please! Don't!
你们这是怎么搞的
What is the matter with you guys'?
没错  大家来说说清楚
Yeah, okay, let's talk it out.
这里只有我一人觉得尴尬吗
Am I the only one that this is embarrassing for?
我也有一点尴尬  嘘嘘
I'm a little embarrassed. Shh, shh.
该尴尬的是你们  这真是可笑
I'll tell you who should be embarrassed. It's you guys. Come on! This is ridiculous!
谢谢你们   但我不需要你们给我安排约会
Thank you very much, but I do not need you to get me a date.
那你为什么叫我们  我还没说完
Then why did she ask us to help-I am still talking!
你们还把我真正喜欢的人赶走
Then you chase away the one guy that I actually liked.
我没有冒犯的意思  真的  恭喜你
I mean, no offense to you guys. Really, congratulations on...
你那么有钱
...all the cash.
还有你   哇   你的头发真柔顺
And you really-Wow, you do have very soft hair.
但我更愿意跟我自己选择的人参加晚会
But I'd much rather go to the ball all by myself than go through any more of this!
再见
Good bye.
你用什么特别的润发露吗
Now, do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?
有  木瓜粹取液  谢谢
Yes, papaya extract. Thank you.
好好去玩吧  我会的
So, uh, have a great time down there. I will.
你带那套泳衣了吗   带了
Did you pack that bathing suit? Yeah.
我刚才把它藏起来了   蛮好玩的
It was pretty funny when I hid it for a while, huh?
总之
Anyway. Um...
我还是担心那套泳装
I am worried about that bathing suit.
倒不是因为太暴露   那个呢我不在意
Not because it's revealing, which I'm fine with.
对  我是关心你的健康
No, I'm concerned about your health.
怕你晒到
Um, sun exposure.
放心  我带了一大堆防晒油
Oh, don't worry, I have plenty of sun block.
防晒系数达到30   好吧
It's SPF 30. All right.
如果里面装的真能到30就好了
Well, if what's in the bottle is actually 30.
有时候买的是30   里面只能达到4   我发誓
I mean, sometimes you get 30, sometimes it's 4, and I swear...
有很多  都只是牛奶而已
...more often than not, it's just milk.
罗斯  你放心
Ross, it's gonna be okay.
我不是要去跟一堆男生鬼混
I'm not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys.
我真的很喜欢你  我珍惜我们的关系
I really like you. I like how things are going between us.
真的  对啊
Really? Yeah.
我只是跟朋友们出去放松玩玩
I'm just going down there to relax and hang outwith my friends.
好吧  酷
Okay. Cool. Heh.
喔  他们来了  嘿  伊丽莎白
Oh, here they are. Hey, Elizabeth!
拜
Bye!
打电话给我
Call me!
瑞秋   抱歉把那些人硬塞给你
Rachel, we're sorry for pushing those guys on you.
没关系   我玩得很开心
That's all right. I ended up having a really good time.
晚会很成功  募到了很多款  而且受到了关注
Y'know, the charity was a big success, they raised a lot of money and awareness.
到底  为什么募款
So, what was it for, anyway?
好像是一种疾病吧
I wanna say a disease.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
罗斯留了条奇怪的信息   叫我们看MTV台
I just got this weird message from Ross. He said turn on MTV. I don't know.
看  天啊  是伊丽莎白
Oh, my God, look! That's Elizabeth! Ha-ha-ha.
喔  盖勒教授
Oh, oh, Professor Geller.
啊哈   重温13岁旧梦   是啊
Ah, to be 13 again. Yeah.